Register of the Pasternak Family Papers, 1877-2012
Hoover Institution Archives
- PASTERNAK TRUST ARCHIVES, 1877-2012; 118.0 boxes
  - LYDIA PASTERNAK SLATER FILE, 1917-1989; 70.0 boxes
    - Correspondence, 1918-1989 (Box 63-110)
      - General, 1918-1989 and undated (Box 65-110)
        - Rainbird McLean Ltd./George Rainbird Ltd., 1960-1965
        - Raine, Olive and Norman, 1972-1973
        - Raleigh, J., 1980
        - Raleigh, John (Otto Rubenstein), 1974-1982
        - Raleigh, Marta and Sue, 1982
        - Ramage, Richard, 1977
        - Rambeth, Marie, 1964
        - Random House, 1962, 1966
        - Rannit, Alexis, 1956-1984 (Box-folder 95: 1-2)
          - 1956-1962 (Box-folder 95: 1)
          - 1963-1984 (Box-folder 95: 2)
        - Rastall, Paul, 1971 (Box-folder 95: 3)
        - Ravet, Eugenie, 1941-1964
        - Reader’s Digest, 1966-1978
        - Realities Magazine, 1963-1966 and undated
        - Reck, Vera, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 95: 4)
        - Record Sales Ltd., 1959-1960
        - Reddaway, Peter (Box-folder 95: 5)
        - Reëm, Ido, 1967-1979
        - Regitz, Traudl and Rudi, 1965
        - Reichsbund Deutscher Akademikerinnnen im Deutschen Frauenwerk, 1935
        - Reiss, E., 1966
        - Reley, Dorothy, 1958
        - Rendell, Audrey, 1967
        - Reshchikova, Vera, 1960s
        - Rey, Eveline, 1967-1968
        - Rey, N., 1970 (Box-folder 95: 6)
        - Richards, Bernard, 1961
        - Richards, Paul, 1970
        - Rijksuniversiteit te Leiden, 1975
        - Rippelino, Angelo Maria, 1963
        - Ritsinova, Vera, 1965
        - Roaf, Dermot, 1959, 1972
        - Robber, Hans, 1965
        - Robert Hale Ltd., 1962
        - Robert, Paolo, undated
        - Roberts, John P., 1972-1974
        - Robertson, Buckley and Co. Ltd., 1962-1964
        - Robertson, Ian, 1949-1982 and undated (Box-folder 95: 7-8)
          - 1949, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 95: 7)
          - 1973-1982 and undated (Box-folder 95: 8)
        - Robillard, René, undated (Box-folder 95: 9)
        - Robinson, Maria, 1973
        - Robson Books Limited Publishers, 1974
        - Robson, Jeremy, 1961-1969 and undated
          Includes letters from Edward Gold, 1961
        - Rodas, Virginia, 1981
        - Rodjun(?), Alan, 1971
        - Roginskaia, Ada, 1964-1973 (Box-folder 95: 10-11)
          - 1964-1967 (Box-folder 95: 10)
          - 1968-1973 (Box-folder 95: 11)
        - Roggei, Olga, 1974 (Box-folder 95: 12)
        - Rojankovsky, Feodor and Nina, 1959-1964
        - Rosbough, David, 1969-1970
        - Rosenfeld, Ernst, 1926-1969
          - Incoming, 1926-1929 (Box-folder 96: 1--6)
            - 1926-1927 (Box-folder 96: 1)
            - 1928 (Box-folder 96: 2-3)
            - 1929-1939 (Box-folder 96: 4)
            - 1953-1963 (Box-folder 96: 5)
            - 1964-1969 (Box-folder 96: 6)
          - Outgoing, 1920s, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 96: 7-9)
            - circa 1920s (Box-folder 96: 7)
            - 1927 (Box-folder 96: 8)
            - 1928 (Box-folder 96: 9)
        - Rosenfeld, Ernst and Hedwig, 1970-1988 (Box-folder 96: 10-12)
          - 1970-1976 (Box-folder 96: 10)
          - 1977-1983 (Box-folder 96: 11)
          - 1984-1988 (Box-folder 96: 12)
        - Rosenfeld, P., 1958 (Box-folder 97: 1)
        - Rosenfeld, R., 1922-1945
        - Rosenthal, A., 1960
        - Rosenthal, Malorie, 1945
        - Roth, Cecil, 1943
        - Rowland, Mary, 1962-1968 and undated (Box-folder 97: 2)
        - Rowlins, Robert, 1971 (Box-folder 97: 3)
        - Rowolt Taschenbuch Verlag Gmbh, 1964-1966
        - Royal Mail Lines, 1970
        - Royal Scottish Academy of Music, 1969
        - Rubbra, S., 1965
        - Rudmin, N., 1947
        - Rudolf, Anthony, 1976
        - Ruggier, Joe, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 97: 4)
        - Ruserford, Z., 1968 (Box-folder 97: 5)
        - Russel, John, 1958-1962
        - Russel, Madeline, 1963-1988 and undated (Box-folder 97: 6-11)
          - 1963-1974 (Box-folder 97: 6)
          - 1982-1984 (Box-folder 97: 7)
          - 1985 (Box-folder 97: 8)
          - 1986-1988 (Box-folder 97: 9)
          - undated (Box-folder 97: 10-11)
        - Russel, Peter, 1958-1964 and undated (Box-folder 98: 1)
          Includes legal documents.
        - Russian Review, 1960
        - Rutherston, Max, 1980
        - Ryabinin (Rayburn), A., 1964-1969 (Box-folder 98: 2)
        - Ryan, Michael, 1983 (Box-folder 98: 3)
        - Saab, Ibrahim, undated
        - Sabetay, Hermine, 1966-1968, 1983
        - Sabetay, Sébastien, 1961-1969
        - Saderman, Anatol and Nina, 1939-1986 and undated (Box-folder 98: 4-10)
          - 1939, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 98: 4)
          - 1962 (Box-folder 98: 5)
          - 1963-1964 (Box-folder 98: 6)
          - 1965-1967 (Box-folder 98: 7)
          - 1968-1969 (Box-folder 98: 8)
          - 1970-1986 (Box-folder 98: 9)
          - undated (Box-folder 98: 10)
        - St. Anne’s Society, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 98: 11)
        - St. Antony College, Oxford, 1958, 1979-1982
        - St. Catherine’s-on-the-Hill Community Project, 1969
        - St. Cross College, Oxford, 1985
        - St. Hugh’s College, Oxford, 1986
        - St. John Ambulance Brigade, County of Oxford, 1967, 1972
        - St. Philip and St. James’s Vicarage, Oxford, 1971
        - Salys (Gaigalas), Rimgaila (Rima), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 98: 12)
        - Salus, Fritz, 1955 (Box-folder 99: 1)
        - Samuels, Josephine, 1961
        - Samuelson, Maurice, 1986
        - Sandberg, Henri, 1971- 1975
        - Sanders of Oxford, 1961-1964
        - Sandor, Gyorgy, 1968
        - Sangster, David F., 1968
        - Sandwith, Hermione, 1968-1976 and undated
        - Saram, Miriam de, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 99: 2)
        - Saram, Rohan de, 1973
        - Savvage, Beryl, 1969
        - Savvage, Stephen, 1973
        - Sayeeda Publictions, 1981
        - Scammel, Michael, 1981
        - Scanlav, Patrick, 1982
        - Schalit, Clara, 1964
        - Scharfenberg, Renate, circa 1960
        - Schechter, Fran, 1970, 1972
        - Schenker, Alexander M., 1964
        - Schiller, Allan, 1966
        - Schiller Nationalmuseum, 1962-1978 (Box-folder 99: 3)
        - Schlögel, Karl, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 99: 4)
        - Schmoller, Hans, 1976-1977
        - Schmucker, Walter, Jr., 1963-1968
        - Schnack, Ingeborg, 1962-1963
        - School of Art, English Bridge, Shrewsbury, 1969
        - Schragerman, Vera, 1980, 1986
        - Schulz-Hoffman, Carla (see also: Bayerischen Staatsgemäldesammlungen), 1979
        - Schumacher, Walter, 1973
        - Schütz, Ann, 1987
        - Schveller (Schüller?), Erna, 1945
        - Schweitzer, Renate, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 99: 5-6)
          - 1961-1962 (Box-folder 99: 5)
          - 1967-1970 (Box-folder 99: 6)
        - Schwenke, G., 1976 (Box-folder 99: 7)
        - Schwester, Boris, 1966
        - Sckolnik, Lewis, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 99: 8)
        - Scottish National Gallery of Modern Art, 1979 (Box-folder 99: 9)
        - Scottsman, the week-end magazine, 1965-1966
        - Seelig, Carl, 1957-1961 and undated (Box-folder 99: 10)
        - Segal, D., 1975 (Box-folder 99: 11)
        - Seibel-Krouse, Hedwig and Hermann Seibel, 1961-1962
        - Seitz, Paul, 1973
        - Sell, Anthony, 1962-1963
        - Senior Wives’ Fellowship, 1964
        - Senter, John and Sue, 1984
        - Serejski, M., 1934
        - Sergeant, Howard, 1962
        - Seymour-Smith, Martin (see also: Scottsman), 1964-1965
        - S. Fischer Verlag, 1960-1962, 1986
        - Shafir, Ida, 1978-1982
        - Shahnovitch, Anna, 1966 (Box-folder 100: 1)
        - Shakespeare Memorial Theatre, 1943
        - Shakhovskoy, Zinaida, 1976
        - Shalders, Ian, 1978
        - Shaw Society, 1958
        - Shaw, Susan, 1966, 1961
        - Shayer, Michael, 1961
        - Sharer, Brooke, 1971
        - Sheikholeslami, Erika, 1974-1975
        - Sheldon, Diana, 1973
        - Sheldon, Richard, 1963
        - Sheldon, Richard, 1982-1985
        - Shelma, Harriet, 1969
        - Shelter, National Campaign for the Homeless, 1972
        - Sherlock, Marjorie, undated
        - Shields, Mike (see also: Orbis), 1981-1985 (Box-folder 100: 2)
        - Shingleton, Peter, 1970
        - Shister, Abram, 1965, 1968
        - Shkarovskaia-Raffe, Natalia, 1987
        - Shmorel, E., 1960
        - Shrewsbury and District Art Association (see also, Barker, Eileen), 1984-1986
        - Shtein, Emmanuil, 1977
        - Shteinberg, A., 1962
        - Shteinberg, Aaaron, 1963-1964
        - Shukman, A., 1970
        - Sicher, Efraim, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 100: 3)
        - Sicloh, Mario, 1984
        - Sieber-Rilke, Hella
        - Siebers Nylander, Lydia, 1976
        - Silbajoris, Rimvydas, 1966
        - Sill, David, 1973, 1979
        - Silva, Preethi(?) de, 1972
        - Silver Age Publishing, 1982
        - Silver, G., undated
        - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box-folder 100: 4)
        - Simmons, J. S. G., 1958
        - Simpson, Joan Murray, 1962, 1972
        - Sinclair, Howard, 1959
        - Sinclair, Patricia, 1969, 1972
        - Skogholm, Carl Werner, 1963
        - Slavin, Lev, 1966
        - Slater, Joanna, undated
        - Slater, Maud, 1943-1963
        - Slater, T., 1963-1964
        - Smallpiece, Vivona, 1958
        - Smirnova, Sofia, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 100: 5)
        - Smith, Dawn, circa 1960, 1974
        - Smith, Dawn and Dennis, 1960-1969 and undated
        - Smith, Jennifer, 1964
        - Smith, Lucy, 1971
        - Smith, Marjorie, 1982-1987 and undated
        - Smith, William G., 1961
        - Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service (SITES), 1984, 1987
        - Snell, Daphne, 1985
        - Snow, C. P., 1964
        - Snowdon, Peter, 1984
        - Snowdon, R. L., 1984
        - Soca, Susana (see also: Verbina, N.), 1957
          Includes a telegram from Susana Soca and information about her correspondence with Boris Pasternak.
        - Social Democratic Party (SDP, Great Britain), 1987
        - Society of Authors, 1958, 1972-1974
        - Society of Friends of Jewish Refugees, 1975
        - Soka Gakkai, 1979 (Box-folder 100: 6)
        - Sollohub, undated
        - SOS Childrens Villages UK, 1982
        - Sotheby’s, 1981, 1987
        - Soukhotine, M., 1962
        - Southend Standard newspaper, 1972
        - South Kent College, 1983
        - South Western Arts Association, 1961-1963
        - "Soviet Literature, 1917-1962" conference
        - Soviet Literature/Sovetskaia Literatura, 1967-1968, 1982
        - Sovetskoe obshchestvo po kul’turnym sviaziam s sootechestvennikami za rubezhom, 1987
        - Soviet Union. Posol’stvo (Great Britain), 1940-1977 (Box-folder 100: 7-8)
          - 1940-1967 (Box-folder 100: 7)
          - 1968-1977 (Box-folder 100: 8)
        - Soviet War News, 1943-1944
        - Soviet Weekly, 1969
        - Sozialdienst Katholischer Männer E.V. Köln, 1966
        - Spat, Judith (Dunia) and Gabriel, 1926-1986 and undated (Box-folder 100: 9-11; 101: 1-3)
          - 1926-1961 (Box-folder 100: 9)
          - 1962-1967 (Box-folder 100: 10)
          - 1968-1969 (Box-folder 100: 11)
          - 1970-1973 (Box-folder 101: 1)
          - 1974-1977 (Box-folder 101: 2)
          - 1978-1986 (Box-folder 101: 3)
        - Sparre-Ulrich, Gertrude, 1946-1983 (Box-folder 101: 4-5)
          - 1946-1967 (Box-folder 101: 4)
          - 1968-1983 (Box-folder 101: 5)
        - Spectator, 1961 (Box-folder 101: 6)
        - Speirs, Ruth, 1962-1964 and undated
        - Spencer, Robin, 1977
        - Spicer, Olive, 1964-1972 (Box-folder 101: 7)
        - Städtische Galerie im Lenbachhaus, 1962-1963 and undated (Box-folder 101: 8)
        - Stakhovich, Maria, 1962-1988 (Box-folder 101: 9-10)
          - 1962-1964 (Box-folder 101: 9)
          - 1965-1988 (Box-folder 101: 10)
        - Stasevich, Vitalii, 1976 (Box-folder 101: 11)
          Includes his letters to Aleksandr L. Pasternak.
        - Stein, Beverly, 1964-1989 (Box-folder 102: 1-6)
          Includes her writings.
          - 1964-1966 (Box-folder 102: 1)
          - 1967-1972 (Box-folder 102: 2)
          - 1973-1976 (Box-folder 102: 3)
          - 1977-1983 (Box-folder 102: 4)
          - 1984-1986 (Box-folder 102: 5)
          - 1987-1989 and undated (Box-folder 102: 6)
        - Stelp and Leighton, Ltd., 1969 (Box-folder 102: 7)
        - Stepherson, John, 1973
        - Stevens, Olive, 1966-1984
        - Stewart, D., 1980
        - Stone, Ella, 1965-1986 and undated
        - Stone, Naomi Celia, 1959
        - Stores, Olive, 1974
        - Störig, Hans Joachim, 1962 and undated
        - Stork, Benedetta, 1982
        - Stork, Joachim W., 1959-1984 (Box-folder 102: 8-9)
          - 1959-1977 (Box-folder 102: 8)
          - 1979-1984 (Box-folder 102: 9)
        - Strizhenko, Adelia, 1970s (Box-folder 102: 10)
        - Struve, Gleb, 1960-1975
        - Stuart, Francis, 1961
        - Studio, the Leading Magazine of Contemporary Art, 1958-1960
        - Studio Ltd., 1945
        - Studio Vista Limited Publisher, 1964
        - Sullivan, Asta, 1960-1964 and undated (Box-folder 103: 1-2)
          - 1960-1962 (Box-folder 103: 1)
          - 1963-1964 and undated (Box-folder 103: 2)
        - Sulzbacher, Martin, 1975 (Box-folder 103: 3)
        - Sulzer (Zivman), Olga, 1973
        - Sundersen, Harriet, 1965
        - Surozhskii, Antonii (Metropolitan Antony of Surozh), 1967
        - Surridge, Les, 1972-1973 and undated
        - Sussex Tapes, 1972-1973
        - Sutherland, Christine, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 103: 4)
        - Sutherland, John, 1969
        - Sutton Court Guild, 1966
        - Swet, Gershon, 1961, 1963
        - Syrodeev, A., 1979
        - Sztein, Emma, 1975-1986
        - Tabidze, Nina, 1961 (Box-folder 103: 5)
        - Tabori, Paul, 1963-1968
        - Tagler, Donald, undated
        - Talbot Rice Art Center, 1978
        - Tanon, Marianne, undated
        - Tarrant, Alison, 1980s
        - Tate Gallery, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 103: 6)
        - Tatham, Andrew, 1978 (Box-folder 103: 7)
        - Taubman, Robert, 1965
        - Tauranga Public Library, 1977
        - Taylor, Dorothy, 1962
        - Terry, Michael, 1978
        - Thames and Hudson Ltd., 1982
        - Thames Television, 1968
        - Theodor Hertzl Institute, 1961
        - Thomas, Don, 1978-1982
        - Thomas, Jane, 1983
        - Thomas Holton, Jane, 1983-1985
        - Thomas, Kay, 1980
        - Thomas, Michael, 1978
        - Thomas, Noëlle, 1969-1985 and undated (Box-folder 103: 8)
        - Thomas, William, 1980
        - Thompson, Leslie, 1961-1972
        - Thores, Esther, 1965-1966
        - Thornton Baker and Co., 1972
        - Thos. Cook and Son, 1964
        - Tidman, Irina, 1971
        - Tilgre, Thea, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 103: 9-10)
          - 1961-1962 (Box-folder 103: 9)
          - 1963-1968 (Box-folder 103: 10)
        - Tisjtjenko Ljunggren, Anna, 1974 (Box-folder 104: 1)
        - Titov, V., 1979
        - Time, the weekly news magazine, 1958, 1982
        - Time-Life Book Division, 1962, 1967
        - Time-Life Foreign News Service, 1962
        - Times, 1945-1972
        - Times Literary Supplement, 1943-1982
        - Todd, Anna, 1984
        - Tolstoi, Ivan, 1986 (Box-folder 104: 2)
        - Tolstoy Foundation, 1965
        - Tom Stacey Ltd., 1972
        - Toporowski, W., 1983
        - Töppelman, Cornelia, 1969
        - Tores, Maria, 1974
        - Torday, Ilona, 1965
        - Toulson, Shirley, 1972
        - Town and Gown Travel, 1978
        - Townsend, Glenda, 1975
        - Toynbee, Margaret, 1968-1969
        - Trade Delegation of the USSR in the UK, 1944
        - Traill, Vera, 1960s
        - Trainina Mira, 1981
        - Transformation, 1943
        - Tretyakov Art Gallery, 1960
        - Tribune, a National Weekly, 1945
        - Trinity, Martin, 1966-1984 (Box-folder 104: 3)
        - Tri-Quarterly, Northwestern University, IL, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 104: 4)
        - Tritsel, Muriel, 1986
        - Trudgill, Jane, undated
        - Tschizewskij, Dmitrij, 1961
        - Tual, Madeline, 1969
        - Tucci, Nicola and Laura, 1959-1864
        - Tuones, Herman, 1929
        - Turchenko, Iurii, 1968
        - Turkay, Osman, 1987
        - Turner, C. M., 1981
        - Turner, Eilliam and Deborah, 1985
        - Turton Geoffrey, 1971
        - Tvardovskii, Aleksandr, 1968
        - Ugrimov (Ougrimoff), A. I., 1965, 1968 (Box-folder 104: 5)
        - Ugrimov, A. A., 1967-1969
        - Umbegaun, Boris, 1959
        - UNA Headquarter Women’s Group, 1972
        - UNESCO Courier, 1979
        - Unggren, Anna, 1982
        - Unicorn, a Quarterly Magazine (See also: Casimir, Paul), 1972
        - Union Européenne D’Éditions (UNÉDIT), 1962 (Box-folder 104: 6)
        - Union Verlag, Stuttgart, 1965
        - United Jewish Relief Appeal, 1944
        - United Nations Library, 1988
        - Universität Mannheim Slavisches Seminar, 1977
        - University College London, 1969, 1972
        - University College of North Wales, Bangor, 1969
        - University College of Wales, 1968
        - University, Keele, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 104: 7)
        - University, Manchester, 1968-1971
        - University of Birmingham, 1972-1983
        - University of Cambridge, 1967-1981
        - University of Cambridge Statistical Lab (see also: Kendall, David, 1972, 1977
        - University of East Anglia, 1976-1978
        - University of Edinburgh, 1968, 1978
        - University of Essex, 1971
        - University of Exeter (see also:Cross, Venetia), 1974
        - University of Hull, 1968
        - University of Kentucky, 1972-1974
        - University of Leeds (see also: Holman, Michael, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 104: 8)
        - University of London, 1960-1980
        - University of London Goldsmiths’ College, 1971-1972
        - University of Manchester, 1959, 1964
        - University of Michigan Press, 1959-1964
        - University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, 1963
        - University of Nottingham, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 104: 9)
        - University of Oxford, 1970-1987
        - University of St. Andrews, 1968-1978
        - University of Stirling, 1978
        - University of Surrey, 1984-1985
        - University of Texas, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 104: 10)
        - University of Toronto, 1960
        - University of Waterloo, 1967
        - Unwin, David, 1967
        - Unwin, Hyman, 1987-1988
        - Unwin Paperback, 1967, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 105: 1)
        - Vanderstay, Sheila, 1976 (Box-folder 105: 2)
        - Vandervoort, Bette, undated
        - Vasil’ev, Oleg, 1976-1977
        - Vasqué, Français, 1978
        - Văyrynen, Anja, 1968, 1972
        - Verbina, N. (see also: Soca, Susana), 1959, 1962
        - Vereinigung der Freunde der Studentschaft der Universität Heidelberg e.V., 1961-1962
        - Verlag Carl Ueberreuter, 1961-1962
        - Verlag der Arche, 1959
        - Vernor-Bright, Anne, 1981
        - Victor Gollancz, Ltd., 1943, 1964
        - Victor Hochhauser, Ltd., 1966 and undated (Box-folder 105: 3)
        - Victoria and Albert Museum, 1959-1967
        - Vienck, Anna, 1963
        - Viereck, Peter, 1960s
        - Viktorova, Tat’iana, 1969
        - Voetsch, Margit, 1973, 1976
        - Voices, a literary quarterly magazine, 1963-1964
        - Volkonskaia, L., 1961-1966 and undated (Box-folder 105: 4)
        - Volkonskii, Oleg, 1962
        - Volkova, T., 1967
        - Volodarskii, V., 1965
        - Voluntary Research Trust of King’s College Hospital and Medical School, 1964
        - Vossius, Dorothea, 1982
        - Vottman, Eva C., 1971 and undated
        - Voznesenskaia, Emilia, 1982
        - Vukanovich, Helen, 1972
        - W. B. Saunders Company Publishers, 1975 (Box-folder 105: 5)
        - W. Colston Leigh, Inc., 1963
        - Wadham, 1971
        - Wagenbach-Wulff, 1985
        - Wain, John, 1967
        - Wainshtein, Lia, 1972-1979
        - Walde, Herman (See also: Il Giorno), 1959-1967
        - Wall, Bernard, 1958
        - Walls, Susan, 1970-1974, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 105: 6)
        - Walton, Margaret, 1985 (Box-folder 105: 7)
        - Ward Gallery, 1961
        - Wardale, Rosemary O., 1972
        - Warrington, Marriah, 1983
        - Watkins, Nina, 1967-1968
        - Watt (Lorell), Hannah, 1968
        - Warwick Gallery, 1973
        - Webster, Audrey, 1951, 1972
        - Weidenfeld (Publishers), Ltd., 1982
        - Weil, Josef, 1963
        - Weilguni, Romana, 1983-1984
        - Weinberg, Simon (Schimon), 1959-1978, 1983 (Box-folder 105: 8-10; 106: 1)
          - 1959-1962 (Box-folder 105: 8)
          - 1963-1965 (Box-folder 105: 9)
          - 1966-1972 (Box-folder 105: 10)
          - 1973-1978, 1983 (Box-folder 106: 1)
        - Weinweiller, Gabriele, 1945 (Box-folder 106: 2)
        - Welch, C. H., 1967
        - Wells, Eleanor, 1967-1970
        - Wells-Marie, Rosemary (see also: Poésie vivante), 1965-1972
        - Welt, Die, 1974 (Box-folder 106: 3)
        - Wesson, Robert G., 1962
        - Weston-Super-Mare Society of Arts, 1962
        - Wharton, Peter, undated
        - Wheat, C. E., 1961, 1972
        - Wheatley, P., 1975
        - Whise-Hustal, Patrick, undated
        - White, Isabel, 1963, 1967
        - Whitechapel Art Gallery, 1960
        - Whitehead, Lorraine, 1966
        - Whitmore, Alice, 1973
        - Whitney, Madeline, 1966
        - Whytes, Alistair, 1969
        - Wilby, C. A., 1974
        - Wilenkin, Marc, 1957
        - Wilhains, Catherine, 1976
        - Wilhelm Fink Verlag, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 106: 4)
        - Wilkinson, Eric (Box-folder 106: 5)
        - Willet, John and Jerri, 1970-1985
        - Wiliam Blackwood and Sons Ltd., 1968
        - Williams, Alan, 1954-1988 and undated (Box-folder 106: 6-10)
          - 1954-1966 (Box-folder 106: 6)
          - 1967-1972 (Box-folder 106: 7)
          - 1973-1976 (Box-folder 106: 8)
          - 1977-1978 (Box-folder 106: 9)
          - undated (Box-folder 106: 10)
        - Willis, Marette, 1963 (Box-folder 107: 1)
        - Willis, Z. W., 1969
        - Wilmers, Charles, 1945
        - Wilmers, Julia, 1945
        - Wilson, A.T., 1964
        - Wilson, Ann, 1971
        - Wilson, Edward, 1966-1973 and undated (Box-folder 107: 2)
        - Wilson, Elisabeth, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 107: 3)
        - Wiltshire County Council, 1961-1962
        - Winfield, Helen Oscar, 1961
        - Winston, Connie
        - Winter, Elizabeth, 1968-1969 and undated
        - Wolf, Arnošt, 1967
        - Wolff, Kurt, 1959-1963 and undated (Box-folder 107: 4-5)
          - 1959-1960 (Box-folder 107: 4)
          - 1961-1963 and undated (Box-folder 107: 5)
        - Wolff, Helen, 1959-1987 (Box-folder 107: 6-7)
          - 1959-1969 (Box-folder 107: 6)
          - 1971-1987 (Box-folder 107: 7)
        - Wolfson, Hazel, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 107: 8)
        - Wolfson College, 1968
        - Woloster, Margaret, 1973
        - Wood, Michael, 1965-1966
        - Woods, Danielle, 1975
        - Worcester College of Education, 1965
        - Workshop Poésie d’Europe, 1976-1980
        - World Jewish Relief, 1978
        - World Poetry (see also: Poet), 1981, 1987
        - World Poetry Society (see also: Poet, 1972-1983
        - Woronoff, A., 1930
        - Wright, Martha, 1967-1968
        - Wright, R. G., 1974
        - Wulff, Elsebeth, 1982-1988 and undated (Box-folder 107: 9)
        - Wurst, Martin de, 1963 (Box-folder 107: 10)
        - Wykeham Hurford, John L., 1968
        - Wylma Wayne Fine Art, 1983-1984
        - Yakobson, Sergius, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 107: 11)
        - Yale University, 1963
        - Yarmolinsky, Avraham, 1982
        - Ylla, Bernat, undated
        - Youth Hostels Association, 1972
        - YMCA, 1966
        - Zaguskin, Jacob (Yakov), 1936-1978 and undated (Box-folder 108: 1-5)